Guide to the New-York Historical Society Museum Department Records 1765, 1830-2018 NYHS-RG 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Collection Management Files, 1929-2005; 167871; 25.38 Linear feet
  - Subseries IV.B. Outgoing Loans, 1939, 1947, 1976-2005; 1976-2002; 109501; 20.21 Linear feet
    - OLR-1986.13. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1985-1986; 110106 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.14. The Parrish Art Museum, 1985-1987; 110107 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.15. Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service, 1985-1989; 110134 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
      Includes photographic prints of the requested item(s) showing a conservation issue.
    - OLR-1986.16. Staten Island Historical Society, 1986-1988; 110143 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
      Includes issue of the Staten Island Historian newsletter dedicated to the exhibition.
    - OLR-1986.17. University Art Gallery, State University of New York at Albany, 1985-1986; 110144 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.18. Tennessee State Museum, 1985-1987; 110145 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.19. Krannert Art Museum, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 1986-1987; 110108 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
      Includes exhibition catalogue.
    - OLR-1986.20. Museum of Art, Rhode Island School of Design, 1985-1986; 110148 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.21. Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, 1985-1986; 110109 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.22. The Hudson River Museum, 1985; 110110 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.23. Albany Institute of History and Art (1 of 2), 1985-1986; 110111 (Offsite-box 7, Folder unknown container)
      Includes exhibition brochure and what appear to be N-YHS exhibit label(s).
    - OLR-1986.23. Albany Institute of History and Art (2 of 2), 1985-1986; 110307 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.24. Museum of the Borough of Brooklyn, Brooklyn College, 1985-1986; 110120 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1986.25. The Magazine ANTIQUES, 110121 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1986; 110123 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1986; 110126 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1985-1986; 110292 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Hopper House Art Center, 1986; 110291 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1985-1986; 110309 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1986 (2 folders), 1984-1986; 110122 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
      Includes color slides of a requested watercolor Perspective View Near Newport, Rhode Island (x.483).
    - OLR-1987.3. The Anacostia Neighborhood Museum, Smithsonian, 1986-1988; 110150 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.4. Bowdoin College Museum of Art, 1984-1987; 110151 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.6. Delaware Art Museum, 1986-1987; 110152 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.7. Huntington Galleries, 1986-1987; 110153 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.8. International Exhibitions Foundation (1 of 2), 1986-1988; 110268 (Offsite-box 8, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.8. International Exhibitions Foundation (2 of 2), 1986-1988; 110262 (Offsite-box 9, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.9. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1986-1988; 110245 (Offsite-box 9, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.10. Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 110254 (Offsite-box 9, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.11. The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1986-1988; 110246 (Offsite-box 9, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.12. National Museum of Science and Technology (Canada), 1987-1988; 110247 (Offsite-box 9, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.13. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1986-1988; 110257 (Offsite-box 9, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.14. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian (2 folders), 1985-1988; 110248 (Offsite-box 10, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.15. The New York Public Library, 110249 (Offsite-box 10, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.16. Philadelphia Maritime Museum, 1986-1987; 110270 (Offsite-box 10, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.17. Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service (2 folders), 1986-1989; 110289 (Offsite-box 10, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1987.18. Gettysburg National Military Park, National Park Service (6 folders), 1986-2000; 110250 (Offsite-box 10, Folder unknown container)
      This set of folders contains documentation regarding the long-term loan, additional items loaned, conservation treatment, a theft of a cutlass (object 1925.103), an extension of the loan, and return of the loaned items. Includes photographic prints (some of which are polaroid) and color treatment slides of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1987.19. The Navy Museum, Department of the Navy, 1984-1992; 110713 (Offsite-box 48, Folder unknown container)
      Includes Kodak instant film photographic prints of certain requested item(s)
    - Museum: The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1987; 110244 (Offsite-box 10, Folder unknown container)
      Concerns a loan of Frederick Remington's Bronco Buster sculpture for the purpose of comparison.
    - Museum: The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1987-1988; 110311 (Offsite-box 10, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Mottahedeh, 1987-1989; 110312 (Offsite-box 10, Folder unknown container)
      Concerns a reproduction arrangement with Mottahedeh with respect to reproduction of a piece of Staffordshire plate.
    - Library: Abigail Adams Smith Museum, 1987-1988; 110290 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1987-1988; 110316 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Amon Carter Museum, 1986-1988; 110317 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Erasmus Hall High School and Academy of the Arts, 1986-1987; 110318 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Utah Museum of Fine Arts, 1986-1987; 110319 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: International Center of Photography, 1986; 110320 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Fort Stanwix National Monument, National Park Service, 1987; 110321 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Nippon Club, 1987-1988; 110322 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
      includes a memorandum regarding a joint exhibition with the Nippon Club.
    - Library: South Street Seaport Museum, 1987-1988; 110597 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1987 (1 of 2), 1985-1987; 110323 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of certain requested item(s) and also photographic prints of a requesting institution's exhibition space.
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1987 (1 of 2), 1986-1988; 111914 (Offsite-box 48, Folder unknown container)
    - Summaries of Loan Activity, 1986-1988, 110718 (Offsite-box 48, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.1. Amon Carter Museum, 1986-1987; 110363 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.2. Edith C. Blum Art Institute, Bard College, 1987-1988; 110364 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.3. The General Theological Seminary, 1987-1988; 110365 (Offsite-box 11, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.4. Heritage Plantation of Sandwich, 1987-1989; 110366 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.5. The Katonah Gallery (2 folders), 1988-1989; 110367 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.6. Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1987-1989; 110370 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.7. National Academy of Design, 1987-1988; 110372 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.8. National Gallery of Art, Smithsonian, 1988-1989; 110373 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.9. Kunsthistorisches Institut der Freien Universitat Berlin, 1988-1989; 110374 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.10. Philadelphia Maritime Museum, 1987-1988; 110375 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints documenting conservation work performed by the requesting institution following damage to the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1988.11. The Hudson River Museum, 1987; 110714 (Offsite-box 48, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.12. The University of Kentucky Art Museum, 1987-1988; 110376 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1988.13. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1988-1989; 110720 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Luman Reed Exhibition, 1988; 110617 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
      Contains receipts of delivery with respect to Asher B. Durand paintings.
    - Library: The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1988-1989; 110371 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Huntington Museum of Art, 1987-1988; 110377 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Hudson River Museum (2 folders), 1987-1989; 110379 (Offsite-box 12, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Grey Art Gallery, New York University, 1988; 110380 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: New York Public Library, 1988; 110381 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
      Concerns delivery of certain insurance atlases to the New York Public Library for shipment with its similar material to a vendor for color microfilming.
    - Library: Amon Carter Museum, 1988; 110382 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
      Found loose in files and put into a folder created by archivist.
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1988 (3 folders), 1975, 1987-1988, 1993; 110385 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.1. The Brick Presbyterian Church, 110391 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1989.2. Musei Capitolini (2 folders), 110619 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
      Includes some correspondence in Italian.
    - OLR-1989.3. Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1988-1989; 110392 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.4. Lehman College Library, CUNY, 110393 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.5. Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1989-1990; 110620 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.6. Museum of American Folk Art, 1988-1990; 110621 (Offsite-box 13, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.7. Museum of the City of New York, 1987-1989; 110622 (Offsite-box 14, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.8. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian (2 folders), 1988-1989; 110623 (Offsite-box 14, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.9. Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1987-1989; 110394 (Offsite-box 14, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.10. Princeton Historical Society, 110397 (Offsite-box 14, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.11. The Queens Museum, 1987-1990; 110624 (Offsite-box 14, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.12. Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (Paris, France), 1989-1993; 110398 (Offsite-box 14, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.13. Washington State Capital Museum, 1988-1989; 110625 (Offsite-box 14, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.15. National Gallery of Art, 1986-1990; 110774 (Offsite-box 14, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.16. Historic Hudson Valley, 1989-1990; 110775 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.17. The Connecticut Historical Society, 1989-1990; 110783 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1989.18. Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1989-1990; 110782 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
      Includes exhibition brochure. See also folder OL-R1990.12. The Brooklyn Museum.
    - Library: South Street Seaport Museum, 1988-1990; 110787 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Whitney Museum of American Art at Phillip Morris, 1989; 110638 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: City of New York, Municipal Building, 1989; 110399 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Meridian House International, 1988-1989; 110400 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Octagon, The American Institute of Architects Foundation, 1988; 110594 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: U.S. Senate Commission on the Bicentennial, 1988-1989; 110401 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Pierpont Morgan Library, 1988-1989; 110595 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
      Includes exhibition catalogues.
    - Library: Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1988; 110596 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: National Archives, Mid-Atlantic Region, 1989; 110601 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Historic Hudson Valley, 1989; 110604 (Offsite-box 15, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1989 (2 folders), 1988-1989; 110598 (Offsite-box 16, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.2. Museum of the City of New York (2 folders), 1990-1991; 110644 (Offsite-box 16, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.3. The Metropolitan Museum of Art (3 folders), 1989-1991; 110645 (Offsite-box 16, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.4. South Street Seaport Museum, 1989-1990; 110790 (Offsite-box 16, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.5. Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1989-1991; 110791 (Offsite-box 16, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of damage to the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1990.6. The Museum of Modern Art, 110800 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.7. The Octagon, The American Architectural Foundation (2 folders), 1990-1991; 110801 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.8. Mayor's Office, City of New York, 1990-1991; 110802 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
      Concerns loan of Flags on Fifty-Seventh Street, the Winter of 1918 by Childe Hassam for display in Mayor's office.
    - OLR-1990.9. Wadsworth Atheneum, 1990-1991; 110799 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.10. The Museums at Hartwick College, 110798 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.11. The Heckscher Museum, 1989-1990; 110819 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.12. The Brooklyn Museum, 110820 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
      See also folder OL-R1989.18. Corcoran Gallery of Art.
    - OLR-1990.13. The Brooklyn Museum, 1990-1991; 110821 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.14. The Edith C. Blum Art Institute, The Bard College Center, 1985, 1988-1990; 110822 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1990.15. The Berkshire Museum, 1989-1991; 110823 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Comune di Milano (City of Milan, Italy), 1990; 110825 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1990; 110833 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: The Jewish Museum, 1990-1991; 110961 (Offsite-box 17, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Centre Georges Pompidou (2 folders), 1990-1991; 110834 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Jewish Museum, 1990-1992; 110960 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Alice and Hamilton Fish Library, 1990-1991; 110828 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1989-1990; 110830 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Stadt Frankfurt am Mein Historisches Museum, 1990; 110962 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Whitney Museum of American Art, Downtown at Federal Reserve Plaza, 1990; 110963 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Staten Island Historical Society, 1990; 110967 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1989-1991; 110969 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Library of Congress, 1989-1990; 110972 (Offsite-box 18, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1990 (4 folders), 1989-1990; 110646 (Offsite-box 19, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1991.1. The Lockwood-Matthews Mansion Museum, 110978 (Offsite-box 19, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1991.2. The National Museum of Sport (2 folders), 1990-1991; 110979 (Offsite-box 19, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints and photographic print of damage to the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1991.3. National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian, 1989-1991; 110980 (Offsite-box 19, Folder unknown container)
      Includes photographic prints of frame of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1991.4. Mayor's Office, City of New York, 1991-1993; 110993 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1991.5. Katonah Museum of Art, 1991, 1996; 110992 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
      Includes documents relating to two exhibitions.
    - OLR-1991.6. Berry-Hill Galleries, Inc., 1991-1992; 110981 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1991.7. The Octagon, The American Institute of Architects Foundation, 1991-1992; 110982 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
      Includes exhibition checklist.
    - OLR-1991.8. Wadsworth Atheneum, 1989-1992; 110983 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1991.9. The Brooklyn Museum, 1987-1992; 110984 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1991.10. Allentown Art Museum, 1989-1992; 110997 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - Long-term loan: American Museum of Natural History, 1991; 110998 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - Long-term loan: Phelps-James House, Phelps Memorial Hospital Center, 1991; 111014 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - Long-term loan: National Park Service, 1991; 111003 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
      Concerns deaccession and donation of ten of thirteen prints to Federal Hall National Memorial, National Park Service, following a long-term loan to that institution.
    - Museum: Mayor's Office, City of New York, 1991; 110647 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: National Academy of Design, 1991; 110648 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery, University of Nebraska Lincoln, 1991; 110649 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
      Contains research-related request for photograph of Diana of the Tower sculpture by Augustus Saint-Gaudens and additional information such as provenance.
    - Library: Casa Italiana, at Low Memorial Library, Columbia University, 1991; 110999 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Museum of the City of New York, 1991; 111007 (Offsite-box 20, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1991 (5 folders), 1988, 1990-1991; 110650 (Offsite-box 21, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.1. Haggerty Museum of Art, Marquette University (2 folders), 1990-1993; 111067 (Offsite-box 21, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.2. McCord Museum of American History, 1991-1993; 111068 (Offsite-box 21, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.3. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1991-1993; 111069 (Offsite-box 21, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.4. The Metropolitan Museum of Art (3 folders), 1990-1992; 111070 (Offsite-box 22, Folder unknown container)
      Includes photographic negatives and prints of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1992.5. Museum of American Glass, 1991-1992; 111075 (Offsite-box 22, Folder unknown container)
      Includes exhibition catalogue. Includes a key labeled "key for Museum of American Glass Box (ours)."
    - OLR-1992.6. Museo Mediceo (City of Florence, Italy) (2 folders), 1991-1992; 111076 (Offsite-box 22, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of packing related to the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1992.7. Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1991-1993; 111077 (Offsite-box 22, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.8. National Museum of Natural History, Smithsonian, 1992-1993; 111078 (Offsite-box 22, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.9. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian (2 folders), 1991-1993; 111079 (Offsite-box 22, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of the frame of requested item(s).
    - OLR-1992.10. War Memorial Museum of Virginia, 1991-1993; 111089 (Offsite-box 22, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.11. Berliner Festspiele GmbH (2 folders), 1991-1992; 111090 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.12. Agnes Etherington Art Centre, Queen's University, 1991-1992; 111095 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.13. The Octagon, The American Institute of Architects Foundation, 1991-1992; 111096 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.14. The Taft Museum, 1991-1993; 111097 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.15. Sordoni Art Gallery, Wilkes University, 111098 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.16. Gallery of Art, Washington University, 1990-1992; 111099 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.17. National Museum of Natural History, Smithsonian, 1992-1993; 111103 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.18. The Hudson River Museum, 111104 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.19. Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1992-1993; 111105 (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.20. L'Assessorato alla Cultura (City of Rome, Italy) (3 folders), 1992-1993; 111126 (Offsite-box 24, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.21. Florence Griswold Museum, 1991-1993; 111127 (Offsite-box 24, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1992.22. Brandywine River Museum, 1991-1992; 111128 (Offsite-box 24, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Queens Historical Society, 1992; 111130 (Offsite-box 24, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Gracie Mansion Conservancy, 1988-1992; 111106 (Offsite-box 24, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Lake Placid Center for the Arts, 1992; 111154 (Offsite-box 24, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1991-1992; 111149 (Offsite-box 24, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: National Archives and Records Administration, 1991-1992; 111150 (Offsite-box 25, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1990-1992; 111152 (Offsite-box 25, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: High Museum of Art, 1991-1993; 111151 (Offsite-box 25, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1992 (3 folders), 1987-1992; 111153 (Offsite-box 25, Folder unknown container)
    - Summaries of Loan Activity, 1992, 111129 (Offsite-box 48, Folder unknown container)
    - Loan status reports, 1992, 1991-1992; 113898 (Offsite-box 48, Folder unknown container)
      Contains lists of outgoing loans for the period of 1990 to 1992. Also includes information regarding the status of long-term loans as of 1991.
    - OLR-1993.1. Virginia Historical Society, 1992-1993; 111817 (Offsite-box 25, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1993.3. The Baltimore Museum of Art (2 folders), 1991-1994; 111170 (Offsite-box 25, Folder unknown container)